question_data = [{
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming"
                  " pools and drinking water.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Vietnam's national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Pluto is a planet.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "The Sun rises from the North.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and "
                  "Italian. ",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Ping-Pong originated in England",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
]
